The latest Overwatch hero is Sombra.
She is a cute, mexican hacker. Just like me!
Uuh, I'm a hacker.
I don't even like tortilla.
Sombra can hack healthpacks so the other team can't use them.
But sadly, it's only temporary.
So today I'm going to show you how to hack the health packs FOR REAL.
On the TF2 map.
It's easy to do.
In the Overwatch folder there is a file called "Health pack attributes Easy to edit for hackers.idx".
Atributos Del Paquete De Salud Fáciles De Editar Para Hackers.idx
Guess what?
That's a trap and will install
Heroes of The Storm™
You need to think like a fourteen year old hiding porn.
Because that's Blizzard.
Find a folder called "Homework"
Then "New folder", "New folder", "New folder" and there.
Now we can edit the file and that's how you hack Overwatch.
"Nice try hacker // Jeff"
Hah, we're dealing with professionals.
This complicates things.
It means we need to hack the Overwatch servers.
The hardest and most important part of hacking is
finding the IP adress. I hide mine in a
fireproof safe. But I know a bug.
You can find Blizzard's IP if you have a character say "Understood"
17 times. And Blizzard's IP adress is...
27. Brilliant! It's so obvious noone would've guessed it.
After putting a tracker on it I have found a login screen for the servers.
I need a password, and I know how to get every Blizzard password.
When Diablo III had launch problems
supposedly Blizzard's CEO refused to leave
his Habbo hotel room.
Then Blizzard's Habbo passwords have been leaked and we can buy them..
On the DARK WEB.
I'm not goona show you how to access the Dark Web
as it's a hacker secret. But here it is.
Warning for sensitive viewers: the Dark Web has a lot of fucked up and disturbing shit.
Like this website that sells Amiibos but ignores Value Added Tax (also known as VAT)
Or how about X365, that sells
Christmas decorations every day of the YEAR
*mumbling* I just- I just need to get out of here. I'll just grab my passwords and leave.
But now we can enter..
This D.VA is staring at me.
"Hello friend, what are you doing? You've been looking at this health kit the entire game."
He has the exact same voice as me except
a norwegian accent. Could this mean..
"Hey, are we actually the same person
but you are who I really want to be?"
"What? No."
Oh thank God. He's just an account on Battle.net.
I know how to deal with him.
When I was eight, I used to hack the Pentagon.
Go to the US Department website and then
on the URLwrite "/president"
and you will enter the President's personal website.
Here you can "Call in a Nuke Strike", "Pilot a drone", "Assassination!"
That's what I used when I was eight
I thought my friend Matthias had stolen my
hollow Charizard. Turns out it was under the bed.
So, apologies to his family.
You know what SWATing is, right?
Well the president has something called "Navy Sealsing"
and that's what we are going to use.
That was easy, but he is right.
I need to start acting normal so noone notices I'm a master hacker.
But I have the username and password for the outer servers
Jeff... Password...
"AllOverwatchHeroesAreActuallyGay"
Yes! I have entered the outer servers!
But I still need to reach the Core.
This is what the inside of a server looks like.
What you see in front of you are not stars, that's programming.
Each one of those white dots is one code.
"But Kilian, Blizzard engineers spent months learning how to navigate inside the server, you have MINUTES."
Huh, let me teach you a trick.
Travel to a high point on the map and punch a wall.
You should be able to hear the punches inside the server.
Follow the noise to reach the Core server system.
On there, My God! The login screen for the Core servers looks exactly like I thought!
I'm going to have to guess the password.
Probably a random mix between numers, letters and symbols.
"arandommixbetweennumberslettersandsymbols"
Copy... Paste.
Dammit, didn't work!
Wait, could it be "FuckValve"?
I'm in!
This is the Core servers!
Current games... Kilian's Game... Health Pack attributes...
And that's how you hack Overwatch!
Password?!
No way!Overwatch has a JavaScript Mainframe Firewall!
How?! That's military-grade technology!
I heard Steam has one but, but.. but it's gonna take days to crack!
I.. I can't do it.
Oh, this guy again.
"Hey, didn't I kill you?"
"No, they left when they ran out of bullets.
You never told me what you were doing."
"I picked Sombra so I could hack Overwatch but Blizzard
defeated me."
"Sombra? Blizzard? Overwatch?
What game do you think you are playing right now?"
What game... am I playing?
But... Why was the password "FuckValve"?